Register of the Friedrich A. von Hayek papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Original Accession, 1906-1988
  - Mont Pèlerin Society File, 1939-1985
    - Correspondence
      - O'Brien, George, 1948 (Box-folder 78: 23)
      - Offelen, Jacques van, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 78: 24)
      - Orton, William Aylott, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 78: 25)
      - Paton, William A., 1958 (Box-folder 78: 26)
      - Patterson, Gardner, 1958 (Box-folder 78: 27)
      - Petro, Sylvester, 1958 (Box-folder 78: 28)
      - Pew, J. Howard, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 78: 29)
      - Pfister, Bernhard, 1948-1958 (Box-folder 78: 30)
      - Philbrook, Clarence E., 1960-1963 (Box-folder 78: 31)
      - Pinedo, Federico, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 78: 32)
      - Plant, Arnold, 1948-1954 (Box-folder 78: 33)
      - Pobers, Michel, 1967 (Box-folder 78: 34)
      - Polanyi, Michael, 1939-1954 (Box-folder 78: 35)
      - Popper, Karl R., 1947-1949 (Box-folder 78: 36)
      - Possony, Stefan T., 1954 (Box-folder 78: 37)
      - Prawiro, Radius, 1968 (Box-folder 78: 38)
      - Read, Leonard E., 1966 (Box-folder 78: 39)
        Includes telegram from R. Anderson announcing his death, 1983.
      - Reig Albiol, Joaquin, 1959-1979 (Box-folder 78: 40)
      - Rio, Manuel, 1957 (Box-folder 78: 41)
      - Röpke, Wilhelm, 1939-1961 (Box-folder 79: 1)
        Includes correspondence with Philip and Stanley Unwin (George Allen and Unwin Ltd.) and Leonard Woof (Hogarth Press).
      - Rothbard, Murray N., 1958 (Box-folder 79: 2)
      - Samuels, L. H., 1950 (Box-folder 79: 3)
      - Schlippenbach, Marjorie von, 1952-1979 (Box-folder 79: 4)
      - Schmölders, Günter, 1953-1970 (Box-folder 79: 5)
      - Schwartz, George, 1948 (Box-folder 79: 6)
      - Schweizerisches Institut für Auslandsforschung, 1950 (Box-folder 79: 7)
      - Serisier, John F. de B., 1984 (Box-folder 79: 8)
      - Severson, Lewis, 1957 (Box-folder 79: 9)
      - Shand, Alexander H., 1984 (Box-folder 79: 10)
      - Shaw, R. Harland, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 79: 11)
      - Shenfield, Arthur A., 1954-1985 (Box-folder 79: 12)
      - Shenoy, B. R., 1959 (Box-folder 79: 13)
      - Silva Pereira, J., 1984 (Box-folder 79: 14)
      - Simkin, Colin G. F., 1948 (Box-folder 79: 15)
      - Sparks, Frank H., 1955-1957 (Box-folder 79: 16)
      - Spearman, Diana, 1948-1960 (Box-folder 79: 17)
      - Sprott, J. H., 1947-1949 (Box-folder 79: 18)
      - Stigler, George J., 1948-1978 (Box-folder 79: 19)
      - Stuart, G. M. Verrijn, 1948 (Box-folder 79: 20)
      - Sturzo, Luigi, 1957 (Box-folder 79: 21)
      - Suenson-Taylor, Alfred J., 1949-1952 (Box-folder 79: 22)
      - Terborgh, George, 1949-1958 (Box-folder 79: 23)
      - Theroux, David J., 1984 (Box-folder 79: 24)
      - Thompson, Paul W., 1947 (Box-folder 79: 25)
      - Thurn, Max, 1961-1984 (Box-folder 79: 26)
      - Tingsten, Herbert, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 79: 27)
      - Trevoux, Francois, 1946-1950 (Box-folder 79: 28)
      - Truptil, Roger J., 1947-1958 (Box-folder 79: 29)
      - Tugendhat, Georg, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 79: 30)
      - Utermann, Wilhelm, 1957 (Box-folder 79: 31)
      - Van Sickle, John V., 1951-1974 (Box-folder 79: 32)
      - Velasco, Gustavo R., 1946-1958 (Box-folder 79: 33)
      - Verrier, Roberto, 1957 (Box-folder 79: 34)
      - Villey, Daniel and Florence, 1947-1968 (Box-folder 80: 1)
      - Vining, Rutledge, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 80: 2)
      - Vogel, Otto A. V., 1956 (Box-folder 80: 3)
      - Wallis, W. Allen, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 80: 4)
      - Watrin, Christian, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 5)
      - Watts, V. Orval, 1947-1954 (Box-folder 80: 6)
      - Wedgwood, C. Veronica, 1949-1954 (Box-folder 80: 7)
      - Wellington Press, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 80: 8)
      - Welter, Erich, 1957 (Box-folder 80: 9)
      - Wesemann, Hans Otto, 1957 (Box-folder 80: 10)
      - West, Rebecca, 1951-1958 (Box-folder 80: 11)
      - Widemer, Alice G., 1958 (Box-folder 80: 12)
      - Wiegand, G. C., 1958 (Box-folder 80: 13)
      - Willgerodt, Hans, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 80: 14)
      - Wilson, Paul, 1949 (Box-folder 80: 15)
      - Wilson, Thomas, 1951-1958 (Box-folder 80: 16)
      - Winterberger, Gerhard, 1950-1959 (Box-folder 80: 17)
      - Wolman, Leo, 1948-1958 (Box-folder 80: 18)
      - Wood, John B., 1976-1977 (Box-folder 80: 19)
      - Woodward, E. L., 1947 (Box-folder 80: 20)
      - Wright, David MacCord, 1948-1960 (Box-folder 80: 21)
      - Wriston, Henry M., 1947 (Box-folder 80: 22)
    - Directories, 1949-1981 (Box-folder 80: 23)
    - Financial reports, 1949-1964 (Box-folder 80: 24)
    - Minutes
      - Board of Directors meeting, 1948 (Box-folder 80: 25)
      - Council meeting, 1981 (Box-folder 80: 26)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 80: 27)
    - Notes, including re membership (Box-folder 80: 28)
    - Proceedings of general and regional meetings
      - Mont Pelerin, Switzerland, 1947
        - General (Box-folder 80: 29)
        - Addresses
          - Hayek, Friedrich A. von [See Speeches and Writings]
          - Rappard, William E. (Box-folder 80: 30)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 80: 31)
        - Lists
          - Invited people who did not attend (Box-folder 80: 32)
          - Participants (Box-folder 80: 33)
          - Nominees for membership (Box-folder 80: 34)
        - Memorandum of association (Box-folder 81: 1)
        - Minutes of discussions
          - Administrative issues (Box-folder 81: 2)
          - Economic issues (Box-folder 81: 3)
        - Papers (Box-folder 81: 4)
        - Statement of aims (Box-folder 81: 5)
      - Seelisberg, Switzerland, 1949
        - General (Box-folder 81: 6)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 81: 7)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 81: 8)
        - Lists
          - Nominees for membership (Box-folder 81: 9)
          - Participants (Box-folder 81: 10)
        - Memorandum from Karl Brandt (Box-folder 81: 11)
        - Papers (Box-folder 81: 12)
        - President's circular (Box-folder 81: 13)
        - President's report (Box-folder 81: 14)
      - Bloemendaal, Netherlands, 1950
        - General (Box-folder 81: 15)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 81: 16)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 81: 17)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 81: 18)
        - Minutes of Council meetings (Box-folder 81: 19)
        - Papers (Box-folder 81: 20)
        - President's circulars, April and September (Box-folder 81: 21)
      - Beauvallon, France, 1951
        - General (Box-folder 81: 22)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 81: 23)
        - Lists of members and participants (Box-folder 81: 24)
        - Papers (Box-folder 81: 25)
        - President's circular (Box-folder 81: 26)
      - Seelisberg, Switzerland, 1953
        - General (Box-folder 82: 1)
          Includes summary of activities up to 1953 and programs of the first four meetings, as well as proposed program for 1953.
        - Agenda (Box-folder 82: 2)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 82: 3)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 82: 4)
        - Minutes
          - Council meetings (Box-folder 82: 5)
          - General meeting (Box-folder 82: 6)
        - Papers (Box-folder 82: 7)
        - President's circular (Box-folder 82: 8)
        - Secretary's report (Box-folder 82: 9)
      - Venice, Italy, 1954
        - General (Box-folder 82: 10)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 82: 11)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 82: 12)
        - Minutes of Council meeting (Box-folder 82: 13)
        - Papers (Box-folder 82: 14)
        - President's circular and report (Box-folder 82: 15)
      - Berlin, Germany, 1956
        - General (Box-folder 82: 16)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 82: 17)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 82: 18)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 82: 19)
        - Minutes of general meeting (Box-folder 82: 20)
        - Papers (Box-folder 82: 21)
        - President's circular (Box-folder 82: 22)
        - Secretary's circular (Box-folder 82: 23)
      - St. Moritz, Switzerland, 1957
        - General (Box-folder 82: 24)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 82: 25)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 82: 26)
        - Financial report (Box-folder 82: 27)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 82: 28)
        - Papers [See also Speeches and Writings for Hayek's opening address] (Box-folder 82: 29)
        - Papers (Box-folder 83: 1)
        - President's circulars, February and September (Box-folder 83: 2)
        - Secretary's report (Box-folder 83: 3)
      - Princeton, New Jersey, 1958
        - General (Box-folder 83: 4)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 83: 5)
        - List of members and participants (Box-folder 83: 6)
        - Papers (Box-folder 83: 7)
        - President's circular (Box-folder 83: 8)
      - Oxford, England, 1959
        - General (Box-folder 83: 9)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 83: 10)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 83: 11)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 83: 12)
        - Minutes
          - Council meetings (Box-folder 83: 13)
          - General meeting (Box-folder 83: 14)
        - Papers (Box-folder 83: 15)
        - President's report (Box-folder 83: 16)
      - Kassel, Germany, 1960
        - General (Box-folder 83: 17)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 83: 18)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 83: 19)
        - Papers (Box-folder 84: 1)
      - Turin, Italy, 1961
        - Agenda (Box-folder 84: 2)
        - Clipping (Box-folder 84: 3)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 84: 4)
        - Papers (Box-folder 84: 5)
      - Knokke-sur-Mer, Belgium, 1962
        - General (Box-folder 84: 6)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 84: 7)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 84: 8)
        - Minutes of Board and Council meeting (Box-folder 84: 9)
        - Papers (Box-folder 84: 10)
      - Semmering, Austria, 1964
        - General (Box-folder 84: 11)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 84: 12)
        - Lists
          - New directors (Box-folder 84: 13)
          - Participants (Box-folder 84: 14)
        - Papers (Box-folder 84: 15)
      - Stresa, Italy, 1965
        - Agenda (Box-folder 85: 1)
        - Clipping (Box-folder 85: 2)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 85: 3)
        - Papers (Box-folder 85: 4)
        - President's address (Box-folder 85: 5)
      - Tokyo, Japan, 1966
        - General (Box-folder 85: 6)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 85: 7)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 85: 8)
        - Papers (Box-folder 85: 9)
      - Vichy, France, 1967
        - General (Box-folder 85: 10)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 85: 11)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 85: 12)
        - Papers (Box-folder 85: 13)
      - Aviemore, Scotland, 1968
        - General (Box-folder 85: 14)
        - List of participants and nominees for membership (Box-folder 85: 15)
        - Papers (Box-folder 85: 16)
      - Caracas, Venezuela, 1969
        - General (Box-folder 86: 1)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 86: 2)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 86: 3)
        - Papers (Box-folder 86: 4)
      - Munich, Germany, 1970
        - General (Box-folder 86: 5)
        - Minutes of Ad-Hoc Committee meeting (Box-folder 86: 6)
        - Papers (Box-folder 86: 7)
      - Montreux, Switzerland, papers, 1972 (Box-folder 86: 8)
      - Salzburg, Austria, 1973
        - General (Box-folder 86: 9)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 86: 10)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 86: 11)
        - Papers (Box-folder 86: 12)
      - Brussels, Belgium, 1974
        - Agenda (Box-folder 86: 13)
        - Papers (Box-folder 86: 14)
      - Hillsdale, Michigan, 1975
        - Agenda (Box-folder 86: 15)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 86: 16)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 86: 17)
      - Paris, France, 1976 January
        - Agenda (Box-folder 87: 1)
        - Papers (Box-folder 87: 2)
        - Press release (Box-folder 87: 3)
      - St. Andrews, Scotland, general, 1976 August (Box-folder 87: 4)
      - Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1977
        - General (Box-folder 87: 5)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 87: 6)
        - Papers (Box-folder 87: 7)
      - Hong Kong, 1978
        - General (Box-folder 87: 8)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 87: 9)
        - List of participants and nominees for membership (Box-folder 87: 10)
        - Papers (Box-folder 87: 11)
      - Madrid, Spain, 1979
        - General (Box-folder 88: 1)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 88: 2)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 88: 3)
        - Papers (Box-folder 88: 4)
      - Stanford, California, USA, 1980
        - General (Box-folder 88: 5)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 88: 6)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 88: 7)
        - Paper (Box-folder 88: 8)
      - Stockholm, Sweden, 1981 August-September
        - General (Box-folder 88: 9)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 88: 10)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 88: 11)
        - Papers (Box-folder 88: 12)
      - Vina del Mar, Chile, 1981 November
        - General (Box-folder 88: 13)
        - Papers (Box-folder 88: 14)
      - Berlin, Germany, 1982
        - General (Box-folder 88: 15)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 88: 16)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 88: 17)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 88: 18)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 88: 19)
        - Paper (Box-folder 88: 20)
      - Vancouver, Canada, general, 1983 (Box-folder 88: 21)
      - Paris, France, 1984 February-March
        - General (Box-folder 89: 1)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 89: 2)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 89: 3)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 89: 4)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 89: 5)
        - Papers (Box-folder 89: 6)
      - Cambridge, England, 1984 September
        - General (Box-folder 89: 7)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 89: 8)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 89: 9)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 89: 10)
        - Papers (Box-folder 89: 11)
      - Freiburg, Germany, 1985
        - General (Box-folder 89: 12)
        - Agenda (Box-folder 89: 13)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 89: 14)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 89: 15)
        - Papers (Box-folder 89: 16)
    - Programs of first eight meetings (Box-folder 89: 17)
    - Summary of history and aims (Box-folder 89: 18)
  - Writings by Others I, 1917-1984
    Articles, conference papers, essays, forewords to books, speeches, and studies, arranged alphabetically by author.
    - Andreski, S. L. (Box-folder 90: 1)
    - Bartley, William Warren, III (Box-folder 90: 2)
    - Bej, Emil (Box-folder 90: 3)
    - Blumle, Gerold (Box-folder 90: 4)
    - Boaz, David D. (Box-folder 90: 5)
    - Corn, Ira J. (Box-folder 90: 6)
    - Duncan, Ronald (Box-folder 90: 7)
    - Emerson, Alfred E. (Box-folder 90: 8)
    - Gilmour, Ian (Box-folder 90: 9)
    - Kinji, Imanishi (Box-folder 90: 10)
    - Mack, Eric (Box-folder 90: 11)
    - Magg, Walter (Box-folder 92: 2)
    - Opitz, Edmund A. (Box-folder 90: 12)
    - Palme, Olaf (Box-folder 90: 13)
    - Plant, Raymond (Box-folder 90: 14)
    - Rockoff, Hugh (Box-folder 90: 15)
    - Rydenfelt, Sven (Box-folder 90: 16)
    - Salin, Phillip (Box-folder 90: 17)
    - Scarman, Lord (Box-folder 90: 18)
    - Scheuer, Sidney H. (Box-folder 90: 19)
    - Siepmann, Udo (and Klaus-F. Dreyhaupt) (Box-folder 90: 20)
    - Sugden, Robert (Box-folder 90: 21)
    - Taylor, Michael (Box-folder 90: 22)
    - Watsnan, Harold T. (Box-folder 90: 23)
    - Wood, J. Stuart (Box-folder 90: 24)
    - Zylberberg, Meir (Box-folder 90: 25)
  - Oversize Materials, 1977-1987 (Box 91)
    Certificate of appreciation, invitation, and scrapbook.
    - Certificate of appreciation, Camara Oficial de Comercio e Industria de Madrid, 1987
    - Invitation, Koryu Ark (Masatoshi Matsushita) (in Japanese), 1978
    - Scrapbook of clippings re Hayek's trip to Guatemala, 1977
  - Videorecordings I, 1978
    Sixteen interviews of Hayek with various people, on 3/4 inch U-Matic videotape cassettes. Several use copies available on-site for immediate use.
    - Robert J. Chitester (Tape cabinet)
    - James M. Buchanan (Tape cabinet)
    - Robert Bork (Reading room DVD use copy)
      Access
      Use copy reference number: 86002_v_0012439.
    - Robert Bork and Axel Leijonufvud (Tape cabinet)
    - Armen A. Alchian (Reading room DVD use copy)
      Use copy reference number: 86002_v_0012440.
    - Jack High (Tape cabinet)
    - Earlene Craver Leijonufvud (Tape cabinet)
    - Axel Leijonufvud (Tape cabinet)
    - Axel Leijonufvud and Thomas W. Hazlett (Tape cabinet)
    - Leo Rosten (Reading room DVD use copy)
      Use copy reference number: 86002_v_0012441.
  - Photographs I, 1972-1980
    - 2 prints depicting Friedrich A. von Hayek, undated (Envelope A)
    - 4 prints depicting Friedrich A. von Hayek addressing a group in Argentina, 1977 (Envelope B)
    - 1 print depicting the room in the Institute for Wirtschaftswissenschaften at the University of Salzburg, Austria, in which Friedrich A. von Hayek's personal library is housed, 1980 (Envelope C)
    - 1 print depicting Ludwig von Bertalanffy with his staff, undated (Envelope D)
    - 1 print depicting Margit and Ludwig von Mises, 1972 (Envelope E)
- Incremental Materials I, 1922-2003
  The following papers comprise the first of four sections of incremental materials of the Friedrich A. von Hayek papers. The materials were received after Hayek's death from his family and his longtime secretary, Charlotte Cubitt.
  - Biographical File II, 1955-1992
    Articles, awards, certificates, clippings, comments, correspondence, distribution list, fellowships, inventory, itineraries, plans, and printed matter, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
    - Articles and clippings about Hayek, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 93: 1)
    - Autograph requests, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 93: 2)
    - Awards and fellowships, 1962-1990 (Box-folder 93: 3)
      Certificates and correspondence from the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, the American Academy of Public Affairs of Los Angeles, and the International Society for Intercommunication of New Ideas
    - Biographical information, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 93: 4)
      Correspondence and printed matter regarding various Who's Who publications
    - Birthday greetings, 1984 (Box-folder 93: 5)
    - Distribution list (Box-folder 93: 6)
    - Honors, 1989 (Box-folder 93: 7)
      Letter concerning Hayek's receipt of the "Grosse Goldene Ehrenzeichen" distinction from Austria
    - Inventory of personal library (Box-folder 93: 8)
    - Itineraries, 1975-1984 (Box-folder 93: 9)
    - Miscellany, 1961 (Box-folder 93: 10)
      Consists of Hayek's comments on smoking
    - Plans for writing, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 93: 11)
  - Correspondence II, 1933-1992
    Letters arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
    - General
      - General
        - Letters requesting recommendations (Box-folder 93: 12)
        - Letters requesting reprint permission (Box-folder 93: 13)
      - A (Box-folder 93: 14)
      - B (Box-folder 93: 15)
      - C (Box-folder 94: 1)
      - D (Box-folder 94: 2)
      - E (Box-folder 94: 3)
      - F (Box-folder 94: 4)
      - G (Box-folder 94: 5)
      - H (Box-folder 94: 6)
      - I (Box-folder 94: 7)
      - J (Box-folder 95: 1)
      - K (Box-folder 95: 2)
      - L (Box-folder 95: 3)
      - M (Box-folder 95: 4)
      - N (Box-folder 95: 5)
      - O (Box-folder 95: 6)
      - P (Box-folder 95: 7)
      - Q (Box-folder 95: 8)
      - R (Box-folder 95: 9)
      - S (Box-folder 96: 1)
      - T (Box-folder 96: 2)
      - U (Box-folder 96: 3)
      - V (Box-folder 96: 4)
      - W (Box-folder 96: 5)
      - X-Z (Box-folder 96: 6)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 96: 7)
    - Adams, Kenneth A. H., 1978 (Box-folder 96: 8)
    - Akademie der Wissenschaften zu Berlin, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 96: 9)
    - Alberts-Ludwigs-Universität Freiburg im Breisgau
      - 1981-1984 (Box-folder 96: 10)
      - 1985-1991 (Box-folder 97: 1)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Gottfried Haberler), 1984-1991 (Box-folder 97: 2)
    - American Spectator (R. Emmet Tyrell, Jr.), 1977-1984 (Box-folder 97: 3)
    - Arias Sanchez, Oscar, 1988 (Box-folder 97: 4)
    - Beltran, Lucas, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 97: 5)
    - Bethmann, Johann Philipp von, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 97: 6)
    - Blackwell Publishers, 1962-1992 (Box-folder 97: 7)
      Includes correspondence with Blackwell's bookstore.
    - Bluestocking Press, 1989 (Box-folder 97: 8)
    - Britain in Pictures Ltd., 1946 (Box-folder 97: 9)
    - Bruges Group, 1989 (Box-folder 97: 10)
    - Bush, George, 1991 (Box-folder 97: 11)
    - Carl Menger Institut (Albert H. Zlabinger), 1987-1991 (Box-folder 97: 12)
    - Cato Institute (David D. Boaz, Roy A. Childs, Jr., Edward H. Crane III, Robert L. Formani, George H. Pearson),., 1976-1991 (Box-folder 97: 13)
    - Center for the Study of Market Processes, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 97: 14)
    - Centre for Policy Studies, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 97: 15)
    - Centre for Research into Communist Economies, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 97: 16)
    - Council "For the Future of the World's Children,", 1989-1990 (Box-folder 97: 17)
    - Critical Review (Jeffrey Friedman, Gregory R. Johnson), 1986-1991 (Box-folder 97: 18)
    - Cubeddu, Raimondo, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 97: 19)
    - Daily Telegraph (Edward Deedes, William Deedes, Antonia Feuchtwanger, David Holloway, Peter Utley), 1974-1991 (Box-folder 97: 20)
    - Dictionary of the History of Ideas (Philip P. Wiener), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 97: 21)
    - Dostaler, Gilles, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 98: 1)
    - Drexler, K. Eric, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 98: 2)
    - Earhart Foundation, 1970-1984 (Box-folder 98: 3)
    - Economic Affairs (Martin J. Anderson, Arthur Seldon), 1982-1987 (Box-folder 98: 4)
    - Economist (Andrew Knight, Gordon Lee), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 98: 5)
    - Encounter (Irving Kristol, Melvin J. Lasky), 1956-1984 (Box-folder 98: 6)
    - Epoche Stiftung Publizistikunion e.V. (Karl Ludwig Bayer), 1978-1981 (Box-folder 98: 7)
    - Estape, Fabian, 1952 (Box-folder 98: 8)
    - Eugen Rentsch Verlag, 1944-1958 (Box-folder 98: 9)
    - Fischer-Barnicol, Hans, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 98: 10)
    - Fisher, Antony, 1988 (Box-folder 98: 11)
    - Forbes (Ronald Bailey, Malcolm S. Forbes, Jr., James W. Michaels, Harriett Miller, Lawrence Minard, Mathias Nolte, Sheldon Zalaznick), 1976-1989 (Box-folder 98: 12)
    - Frankfürter Allgemeine Zeitung (Jürgen Eick, Fritz Ulrich Fack, Karl Feldmeyer, Klaus Natorp, Ernst Gunter Vetter, Viktoria Schutze, Christopher Schwarz), 1974-1989 (Box-folder 98: 13)
    - Fraser Institute (Walter Block, Walter Davis, John S. P. Robson), 1987-1991 (Box-folder 98: 14)
    - The Free Press (Jeremiah Kaplan, Kitty Moore, John S. Simon), 1951-1984 (Box-folder 98: 15)
    - Freiburg im Breisgau (Germany), 1986-1988 (Box-folder 98: 16)
      Includes correspondence with mayor and regional president.
    - Freiburger Kreis (Gerhard Kempter), 1982-1987 (Box-folder 98: 17)
    - Fritz Knapp Verlag (A. Binz), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 98: 18)
    - Fürth, Herbert J., 1990 (Box-folder 98: 19)
    - George Allen & Unwin Ltd., 1938-1981 (Box-folder 98: 20)
    - Glasner, David, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 98: 21)
    - Goddard, Arthur, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 98: 22)
    - Habsburg, Otto von, 1958-1984 (Box-folder 98: 23)
    - HALT (Human Action to Limit Taxes), 1981 (Box-folder 98: 24)
    - Hanne, Florian, 1989 (Box-folder 98: 25)
    - Hazlitt, Henry, 1964-1984 (Box-folder 98: 26)
    - Heritage Foundation (Edwin J. Feulner, Jr.), 1980-1991 (Box-folder 98: 27)
    - Hoffmann und Campe Verlag, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 99: 1)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace (W. Glenn Campbell, Robert Hessen, Charles G. Palm, John Raisian), 1979-1992 (Box-folder 99: 2)
    - Hutt, William Harold, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 99: 3)
    - Income and Capital Growth Strategies, Inc. (Doug Thorburn), 1988-1991 (Box-folder 99: 4)
    - Independent Institute (David J. Theroux), 1986-1990 (Box-folder 99: 5)